<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CV on Sung Sam Gong, PhD</title>
    <link>/tags/cv/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CV on Sung Sam Gong, PhD</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/cv/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CV</title>
      <link>/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cv/</guid>
      <description>Employment Apr, 2014 – Current: Senior Research Associate in Bioinformatics, Department of Obstetrics &amp;amp; Gynaecology, University of Cambridge, UK Feb, 2015 – Aug, 2017: Visiting Researcher, Wellcome Trust Sanger Institute, Hinxton, UK Sep, 2010 – Mar, 2014: Lead Bioinformatician, Cardiovascular Genetics and Genomics, NIHR Cardiovascular Biomedical Research Unit, Royal Brompton and Harefield NHS Foundation Trust and Imperial College, London, UK Mar, 2011 – Mar, 2013: Honorary Research Associate in Heart Science, National Heart and Lung Institute, London, UK Sep, 2010 – Sep, 2012: Visiting Scientist, MRC Clinical Science Centre, Hammersmith, London, UK Sep, 2005 – Sep, 2006: Research Scientist, KOBIC (Korean Bioinformation Centre), KRIBB (Korea Research Institute of Bioscience and Biotechnology), Daejeon, Korea   Education Oct, 2006 – Aug, 2010: PhD, Department of Biochemistry, University of Cambridge, Cambridge, UK (supervisor: Professor Sir Tom Blundell) Thesis title: Structural and Functional Analysis of Single Amino Acid Replacement in Proteins: Insights from Protein Evolution into the Disease Aetiology [download] Sep, 2003 – Aug, 2005: MSc, Department of BioSystems, KAIST (Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology), Daejeon, Korea (supervisor: Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>edudation</title>
      <link>/edu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/edu/</guid>
      <description>Education Oct, 2006 – Aug, 2010: PhD, Department of Biochemistry, University of Cambridge, Cambridge, UK (supervisor: Professor Sir Tom Blundell) Thesis title: Structural and Functional Analysis of Single Amino Acid Replacement in Proteins: Insights from Protein Evolution into the Disease Aetiology Sep, 2003 – Aug, 2005: MSc, KAIST (Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology), Department of BioSystems, Daejeon, Korea (supervisor: Dr. Jong Bhak) Thesis title: PSIbase and interpare : systems for studying protein structural interactomics Mar, 2002 – Aug, 2003: BSc, Department of Computer Science, Korea University, Seoul, Korea.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>